- Shawty snap, yeah
- T-Pain
- Ah Shawty snap, Yung
Joc, shawty (shawty snap)
- Yeah, yeah, yeah
- Aye, Aye, she snap
- Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh
Yeah, snap yo' fingers, do yo' step
You can do it all by yourself (Woo!)
♪ Baby girl, what's your name ♪
♪ Let me talk to you,
let me buy you a drank ♪
♪ I'm T-Pain, you know me ♪
♪ Konvict Music, Nappy Boy, ooh wee ♪
♪ I know the club close at three ♪
♪ What's the chances of
you rollin' with me ♪
♪ Back to the crib, show you how I live ♪
♪ Let's get drunk, forget what we did ♪
♪ I'ma buy you a drank ♪
♪ And then I'ma take you home with me ♪
♪ I got money in the bank ♪
♪ Shawty, what you think 'bout that ♪
♪ I'll be in the gray Cadillac ♪
♪ We in the bed like ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, woah, woah, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, woah, ooh,
woah, woah, ooh, ooh, whoa ♪
♪ Talk to me, I talk back ♪
♪ Let's talk money, I talk that ♪
♪ Crunk juice bombs, Oakley shades ♪
♪ Shawty got class, oh behave ♪
♪ Let's get gone, walk it
out (Now walk it out) ♪
♪ Just like that, that's
what I'm talkin' 'bout ♪
♪ We gon' have fun, you gon' see ♪
♪ On that Patrón you should get like me ♪
♪ I'ma buy you a drank,
woah, oh-ooh, woah ♪
♪ And then I'ma take you home with me ♪
♪ I got money in the bank ♪
♪ Shawty, what you think 'bout that ♪
♪ I'll be in the gray Cadillac ♪
♪ We in the bed like ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, woah, woah, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, woah, ooh,
woah, woah, ooh, ooh, whoa ♪
♪ Won't you meet me at the
bar, respect big pimpin' ♪
♪ Tell me how you feel, mama
tell me what you sippin' ♪
♪ A certified dime piece,
deserve Louis one three ♪
♪ One fifty a shot, three
for you and three for me ♪
♪ I'm checking your body language,
I love the conversation ♪
♪ And when you lick your lips
I get a tingling sensation ♪
♪ Now were both 'bout tipsy,
you say you in the mood ♪
♪ All I need is 'bout a
hour, better yet maybe two ♪
♪ Let me take you where I
live, Ferrari switch gears ♪
♪ When I whisper in your ear ♪
♪ your legs hit the chandelier ♪
♪ Passion fruit and sex
all in the atmosphere ♪
♪ I'ma let T-Pain sing it
so he can make it clear ♪
♪ I'ma buy you a drank,
woah, oh-ooh, woah ♪
♪ And then I'ma take you home with me ♪
♪ I got money in the bank ♪
♪ Shawty, what you think 'bout that ♪
♪ I'll be in the gray Cadillac ♪
♪ We in the bed like ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, woah, woah, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, woah, ooh,
woah, woah, ooh, ooh, whoa ♪
♪ Let's get gone, walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out think
about it, oh snap ♪
♪ Now rock, rock, rock, rock ♪
♪ You can do it all by yourself ♪
♪ Let's get gone, walk it out ♪
♪ Now walk it out think
about it, oh snap ♪
♪ Now rock, rock, rock, rock ♪
♪ You can do it all by yourself ♪
♪ I'ma buy you a drank ♪
♪ And then I'ma take you home with me ♪
♪ I got money in the bank ♪
♪ Shawty, what you think 'bout that ♪
♪ I'll be in the gray Cadillac ♪
♪ We in the bed like ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, woah, woah, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ooh, ooh, woah, ooh,
woah, woah, ooh, ooh, whoa ♪
(snap)